A Guide to the Studies of the Virginia Division of Legislative Services, 1978-2000.
Library of Virginia
- Studies (Accession 42785), 1991-1999., Extent: 9 cubic feet (9 boxes)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Unauthorized Disclosure of Autopsy and Medical Examination Records (HJR 218), 1998. (Box 1)
    - Reports, research materials, other state laws, correspondence, articles, public hearing comments, audiotapes.
  - Joint Subcommittee on the Statutory Duties and Responsibilities of Church Trustees (HJR 246), 1998. (Box 1)
    - Reports, research materials, correspondence, audiotapes.
  - Judicial Council's Ad Hoc Committee of Local Rules (HB 2522), 1999. (Box 1)
    - Research materials, correspondence.
  - House of Delegates Study Committee on Employer Job Reference Immunity (HB 2465), 1999. (Box 1)
    - Reports, research materials, other state laws, correspondence.
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study the Reorganization of the State Library and Archives (SJR 96, 1994; SJR 258, 1995; SJR 45, 1996; SJR 300, 1997; SJR 173, 1998), 1994-1998. (Box 2)
    - Agendas, Minutes/meeting notes, reports, research materials, correspondence, handouts. Senate Document 53 (1995); Senate Document 31 (1999).
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Human Immunodeficiency Virus (HIV) (HJR 31, 1991; SJR 28, 1991; HJR 436, 1992; HJR 692, 1993 and 1994), 1991-1994. (Box 3)
    - Agendas, minutes/meeting records, study plans, research materials, correspondence. House Document 56 (1991); House Document 17 (1992); Final Report 1993 - never published.
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Human Immunodeficiency Virus (HIV) (HJR 692, 1994), 1994. (Box 4)
    - Agendas, minutes/meeting records, reports, research materials, correspondence, handouts, audiotapes.
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Human Immunodeficiency Virus (HIV) (HJR 692, 1994; HJR 567, 1996; HJR 132, 1996-1997; HJR 269, 1998-1999), 1994-1999. (Box 5)
    - Agendas, minutes/meeting records, study plans, reports, research materials, correspondence, handouts, presentations.
  - State Water Commission to Study Indoor Plumbing Needs for Southwest Virginia (HJR 272, 1998), 1998-1999. (Box 6)
    - Agendas, minutes/meeting records, study plans, reports, research materials, correspondence, handouts, presentations, public hearing comments. House Document 67 (1999); Economic Analysis of Water Hauling for Southwest Virginia.
  - State Water Commission with Virginia Water Resources Research Center to Study Drinking Water in Southwest Virginia (HJR 592, 1997), 1997-1998. (Box 6)
    - Agendas, minutes/meeting records, reports, research materials, correspondence, presentations, audiotapes. House Document 67 (1999); Economic Analysis of Water Hauling for Southwest Virginia.
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Mandatory Boating Safety Education in Virginia (HJR 174, 1998), 1998-1999. (Box 7)
    - Agendas, minutes/meeting records, study plans, reports, research materials, other state laws, correspondence, legislation, presentations, public hearing comments, handouts, audiotapes. House Document 68 (1999); Economic Analysis of Water Hauling for Southwest Virginia.
  - Commission on the Commonwealth's Planning and Budgeting Process (SJR 350, 1997; SJR 94, 1998), 1997-1999. (Box 8)
    - Agendas, minutes/meeting records, reports, research materials, other state laws, legislation, correspondence, articles, presentations, handouts. Senate Document 28 (1999).
  - Joint Subcommittee Studying Ways to Enhance the Supply of Vital Organs (HJR 100, 1996; HJR 627, 1997), 1996-1999. (Box 6)
    - Minutes/meeting records, reports, research materials, other state laws, correspondence, articles, handouts. House Document 9 (1999).
- Studies (Accession 43390), 1986-2000., Extent: 38 cubic feet (38 boxes)
  - Joint Subcommittee to Study Current Means and Adequacy of Compensation to Virginia Citizens Whose Properties are Taken Through the Exercise of Eminent Domain (SJR 271) and Joint Subcommittee to Study Compensation for Property Taken by Eminent Domain (HJR 491), 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Agendas, minutes / meeting notes, reports, research material, other state laws, legislation, correspondence, articles, presentation, public hearing comments, handouts. Senate Document 53 (2000). 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Correspondence and notes, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Alternate procedure, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Background briefing, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Billboards and business losses, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Cases, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Condemnation blight, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Condemnation information, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Legislation, 1990-1999. (Box 1)
    - Meeting, 1999 July 21. (Box 1)
    - Meeting, 1999 Aug 24. (Box 1)
    - Meeting, 1999 Dec 10. (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Newspaper articles, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Public hearing - Salem, 1999 July 21. (Box 1)
    - Public hearing - Newport News, 1999 Oct 6. (Box 1)
    - Side by side comparisons, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - State Corporation Commission - Transmission line guidelines, 1999-2000. (Box 1)
    - Work session, 1999 Nov 16. (Box 1)
    - Work session, 2000 Jan 10. (Box 1)